Don't Kill It is a fantasy, horror, action film directed by Mike Mendez.
Demon hunter Jebediah Huntley teams up with an FBI agent to battle a
supernatural force in the southern state of Mississippi.
Jebediah Woodley, played by Dolph Lundgren.
Pastor Erikson, played by James Chalke.
Agent Evelyn Pierce, played by Kristina Klebe.
Agent Jackson, played by Billy Slaughter.
Deacon Shepard, played by Miles Doleac.
sexy demon, played by Elissa Dowling.
Don't Kill It is a 2016 American comedy horror film
directed and edited by Mike Mendez.
Written by Dan Berk and Robert Olsen, it stars Dolph Lundgren as Jebediah Woodley, a demon hunter
who travels to Mississippi in the hopes of destroying an ancient, homicidal demon.
Kristina Klebe, Tony Bentley, James Chalke, and Miles
Doleac appear in supporting roles.
Mendez was attached to direct for over four years.
Originally set in Alaska, once green-lit the script was altered and
filming moved to Mississippi over financial concerns.
The budget was less than $1 million, with $15,000 of it
raised via the crowdfunding website Indiegogo.
Lundgren was cast around 9–10 months before filming commenced,
whilst Klebe only had one-to-two weeks notice.
After being postponed twice, principal photography commenced over the
2015 Christmas holiday season in Lexington, Mississippi.
Filming concluded after 17 days of shooting, with the film having its premiere
at the Fantasy Filmfest in Hamburg, Germany, on August 27, 2016.
This was followed by the North American premiere on September
26, 2016, at Fantastic Fest in Austin, Texas.
A limited theatrical release followed on March 3, 2017, via AMC Theatres.
Opening to mostly positive reviews, Noel Murray of the Los Angeles Times, described
Don't Kill It as one of Lundgren's "most entertaining movies in years."
The film explores themes of fbi, gore, demon, evil, demonic possession.
The tone is dark.